thebattalion.tv 2011-05-25

# Privacy Policy | The Battalion

TFP Privacy Policy  
(1) How to contact us  
(2) Collection of Personal Information  
(3) Collection of Personal Information by Site Partners or Sponsors  
(4) Collection of Non-Personal Data  
(5) Collection of information by Third Partys  
(6) Disclosure of Personal Information  
(7) Content of Emails  
(8) How to Discontinue Online Participation  
(9) How to Change Personal Information  
(10) Retention of Personal Information  
(11) Security of the Personal Information Collected  
(12) Children's Privacy Policy  
(13) Changes to Our Privacy Policy

We take seriously the collection of personally identifiable information from our viewers and work to protect each visitor's privacy in accordance with the terms of this policy. We use the terms "viewers" and "you" to include any person who accesses this website. Please carefully review our privacy practices below. These privacy practices apply to this website and to our family of TULE FOG PRODUCTIONS LLC Sites.

(1) How to contact us

This website is owned and operated by Tule Fog Productions LLC (referred to herein as "TFP," "We," "Us," or "Our, or The Company ). You may contact us directly if you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please Contact Us.

(2) Collection of Personal Information

We provide various informative and/or entertaining features as part of this website. We may also offer opportunities for website interaction or submissions. To provide these features, we may request and collect certain personally identifiable information from our viewers, including, but not limited to, name, email addresses, birth date and other identifying information (referred to herein as "personal information"). We may use collected personal information to distribute our newsletter; respond to viewer s inquiries or requests; allow online submissions; improve our services; protect the security of our viewers, system, service and/or website; for marketing and/or promotional use; and to survey viewers about various topics, including but not limited to their preferences. The personal information collected through this website may be combined and maintained with information we collect offline.

(3) Collection of Personal Information by Site Partners or Sponsors 

Third party partners or sponsors may join with us to offer website features or promotions, such as contests, sweepstakes or special events. For these features, the partner or sponsor of the activity may request and collect your personal information. If you submit personal information in such joint activities, the sponsor or partner may share personal information submitted for the activity with us and/or we may share such information with them. The sponsor or partner may also maintain separate privacy policies governing the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information. Personal information collected in conjunction with such activities may be used for the marketing of additional services, promotions or events. We are not responsible for the collection, use and disclosure practices of third parties.

(4) Collection of Non-Personal Data

GIFs. A clear gif [Graphics Interchange Format] (also known as pixel tags, web beacons or web bugs) is a tiny line of code only 1 by 1 pixel in size that is programmed to collect certain Data about a visit to a particular website, such as how many hits a site link receives or to retrieve track visitor preferences. These devices automatically collect data, including your Internet server and browser identification, Internet service provider, click-through information, the web page from which a view enters our site, web pages visited, usage patterns, duration of site visit and domain type. We may use these devices, and the general information gathered from these devices, to gauge the effectiveness of our website and site features; to tailor our website to specific interests or participation; to simplify site navigation; or to deliver a more personalized website service by recognizing certain choices you have made on our site. We may also use these devices to conduct research, for auditing purposes, or to estimate our audience size. We do not use cookies or gifs to independently collect personal information. However, the aggregate "hits" data collected by these tracking devices may electronically link to some personal information that you have voluntarily provided over our website. We do not disclose this combined information (personal information linked to our cookie and gif collections) to nonaffiliated third parties. To prevent the automatic recording of information through cookies, you can configure your browser to either reject all cookies or notify you when a cookie is sent. If you disable cookie tracking, however, you may find that some areas on the website will be slower or may not function at all.

(5) Collection of information by Third Partys

We may permit advertising on our website by third parties and/or link to the websites of third parties that are not owned or operated by Tule Fog Productions LLC, its affiliates or its sponsors or that do not participate in joint activities with us. These third parties may independently solicit and collect personal information. Please be advised that when you click on an advertisement or link to another website that is not part of the TULE FOG PRODUCTIONS LLC web site, you will be subject to the privacy policy and terms of usage agreement of that advertiser/website operator. Programs or other applications on your computer may cause advertisements not affiliated with us to appear on top of our web pages. We are not responsible for third party advertiser ads, links and/or "pop-ups," or the content, activities, information collection, use and disclosure practices of other third party site operators.

(6) Disclosure of Personal Information

We may disclose your personal information with other parties only when you consent to this disclosure; it is required or permitted by law; it is necessary to operate our website or site features; to complete visitor requests; to protect the safety of our viewers, employees or property; to investigate or help prevent unlawful activity or activity that threatens our network or website; to provide or enhance our website features or operations; to enable participation in contests; to allow receipt of newsletter information; or for program subscription services. The third parties with whom we disclose personal information include our select sponsors or service partners; agents; consultants; content or service providers; entities that provide website operational or promotional support; attorneys; accountants; auditors; authorized government entities or other lawfully authorized parties. We may disclose personal information to other third parties in conjunction with entering into an agreement for the sale of our stock or assets or if we are involved in bankruptcy proceedings. The recipient of personal information following such actions may have privacy policies that differ from those in this policy. We may further disclose the names of viewers to our web site for certain events, such as the winners of our contests. We may disclose aggregate, non-personal information to other parties for other purposes.

(7) Content of Emails

When we communicate with viewers via email, we will protect the privacy of the viewers email address and other personal information consistent with this policy. However, we may disclose the content or portion of the email message that does not contain personal information to other third parties not identified in this policy.

(8) How to Discontinue Online Participation

Online site participation is voluntary. If at any time you choose to discontinue your participation in special site features, such as receiving our newsletter, please use our Contact email for communications with us.

(9) How to Change Personal Information  
You may request that we update or change certain personal information that we collect about you by contacting us via our Contact email on our site. Certain information that we collect may need to be retained for security purposes, in accordance with various laws or per our business retention practices. We retain the right to refuse to change or delete certain personal information.

(10) Retention of Personal Information

We retain personal information for as long as it is needed to maintain our business records in the ordinary course of doing business to preserve our database and website records, to comply with laws governing our business and or if there are authorized requests for retention and/or disclosure from government, law enforcement or the courts. This means that we may retain personal information for years after the initial collection of the data.

(11) Security of the Personal Information Collected

We use reasonable efforts to protect the security of personal information transmitted to us through our website and stored by us. We require our employees to protect the privacy of viewers' personal information and restrict access to databases containing viewers personal information. Please remember that despite our security measures, the transmission of data over the Internet is not guaranteed to be completely secured. Parties not under the control of Rainbow, its parents, affiliates or subsidiaries may intercept or access electronic transmissions or other data without authorization. Thus, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of information you send to or receive from us. Any electronic transmissions that you submit or accept are at your own risk.

(12) Children's Privacy Policy

TULE FOG PRODUCTIONS LLC web site is for general audience usage. We do not target or appeal to children under the age of thirteen and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of thirteen. If upon notification by a parent or guardian, or discovery by other means that a child under thirteen has improperly registered on our web site we will delete the child's personal information from our records and cancel the child's online participation.

(13) Changes to Our Privacy Policy

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time. If we update or change the terms of this Policy, the changes will be posted as a revised Privacy Policy and will be available on our website. Thank you from the staff of Tule Fog Productions LLC
